# JONATHAN LEE

MATHEMATICS AND ECONOMICS STUDENT

#### Seattle, Washington 98125

indeanlee@gmail.com
indeanlee@gmail.com

(206) 466-9242

www.linkedin.com/in/jonathan-lee-4b831025b

https://github.com/JONATHAN-

LEE-01/Portfolio

# **OBJECTIVE**

Detailed-oriented and number driven student with 5 years of restaurant management experience who is seeking to transition into a community focused intern role with LISC. I am ready to combine my fast paced work experience and organizational and communication skills with my interests in economics, finance, and public policy to encourage accessible and inclusive community development.

# **EDUCATION**

### **B.A. Mathematics and Economics**

Western Washington University | Bellingham, WA

Graduation Date: Aug 2023

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Student Ambassador

Western Washington University | Bellingham, WA

Nov 2022 - Present

- Hand-selected to represent the WWU Mathematics Department as a liaison between students and faculty, and the Dean of CSE.
- Designed and implemented the Mathematics Department's first Mentorship Program.
- Sought to engage in issues around advocacy, equity, and diversity in STEM.
- Held weekly office hours to engage with students on topics around advocacy, diversity, equity and experiences in STEM.

### ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

# Server/Person in Charge (PIC)

Server/Person in Charge (PIC) | Bellingham, WA

Aug 2020 - Present

- Counted tills daily to ensure accurate revenue numbers.
- Memorized entire food menu and up to 12 different parties' orders at any given time.
- Communicated efficiently to back of house to execute customer requests accurately.
- Described menu items persuasively to increase sales.

# Lead Line Cook/PIC

Aslan Brewing Co. | Bellingham, WA

Jul 2017 - Nov 2019

- Worked in a high stress environment within a high-volume restaurant
- Facilitated and directed line cooks to execute food menu items accurately in an organized and timely manner.
- Tracked inventory weekly to provide the company with its annual COGS and optimize menu pricing and development.

# Painter's Assistant

MadeRadbyTony | Bellingham, WA

Sep 2017 - May 2019

- · Meticulously prepared bicycles for custom paint.
- Sandblasted aluminum bicycle frames and hand-sanded carbon fiber bicycle frames.
- Most notably, assisted in custom painted bicycles for Jason Momoa and Jill Kintner.

# **ACTIVITES**

Honors Students of Color Member

Nov 2022

WWU Cycling Team Vice President/Race Director

Sep 2019 - Jun 2020